I'm going to drink champagne.
Isn't it good?
I'll put this in.
It looks delicious.
It looks really good.
Cheers!
Let's eat.
It's good.
I'm going to eat.
What is it?
Is it a present?
I'm so happy.
Thank you.
Chocolate?
It looks delicious.
What is this?
It's cute.
Thank you.
I'm glad.
I'm embarrassed.
I'm embarrassed to be with a ghost.
That's not true.
It's amazing.
It's very cute.
It's cute.
Is this a brand?
I've seen it before.
It's a very expensive one.
Did you buy it?
I got this as a present.
I'm her boyfriend.
I have a boyfriend.
I see.
He's kind to me.
He's a very expensive person.
He's a venture capitalist.
A venture capitalist?
Is he a company?
He's a company.
He's the president.
He's amazing.
Cheers!
It's good.
I'm happy to have a drink in the afternoon.
Why do you drink light bar in the afternoon?
I have something to talk about.
Oh, you brought the camera.
I brought it.
It was heavy.
Sorry.
It seems to be recording.
Is it recording?
Yes.
I got watered by customers.
I heard that I'm a famous influencer now.
I met this person the other day.
Look at this.
Look.
It looks delicious.
Where is this?
I went to a restaurant in a luxury hotel from Matterma.
I've been taking pictures all the time.
It's different.
It's so fancy.
It was more plain before.
This is a port girl.
Yes.
I don't know because I'm fat.
I'm touching my phone all the time.
How many likes did you get?
I don't know.
130,000 people.
Did you hear that?
What?
130,000 people.
It's funny.
Aika is like this now.
We talked about the soap.
She hated it at once.
I think that's in the video.
Look at this.
I met the manager.
I went to a restaurant recently.
I met Aika.
I said I wanted to go there.
Do you remember the izakaya near the restaurant?
It was a little old.
Did you see her face?
She said she didn't want to talk anymore.
Let's go there.
It's a good timing.
Do you remember the waiting room where Aika was?
I decorated the waiting room.
There was no girl in the waiting room.
You're laughing at me.
I'm not laughing at you.
I'm laughing at you.
It's fun to drink with everyone.
I'm like that.
I don't want to talk about the old days.
I'm still doing it.
I feel like I've been denied.
I'm sad.
I'm angry.
I'm a little angry.
But the world we live in is different.
What is she doing?
She has a younger manager boyfriend.
She doesn't have money.
She eats and drinks well.
I envy her.
I'm angry.
I'm thinking about something.
What is it?
I'm thinking of raping Aika.
Rape?
I don't understand.
I'm angry.
I'm thinking of raping Aika.
I'm afraid of making my old friends angry.
You want to see it, too.
I'm going to hell.
I'm sorry.
You are amazing.
You look happy.
Let's go.
I'm going.
I'm back.
Welcome back.
What did you do?
You are back.
Congratulations.
What is this?
I was gone.
I was waiting for you.
Congratulations.
Happy birthday to you
Happy birthday dear Aikawa
I did it!
Do it again!
I'll go
Congratulations! Thank you!
I'm so happy!
Thank you!
Aikawa, you must be tired from all the work you did today
I'm so happy! I'm so tired
I thought you'd be fine
I'm so happy!
I'll do my best
Let's do our best!
By the way, tomorrow we'll be back early
Really?
Don't drink until then!
I'll be drunk
We used to make money by using our bodies.
But now, I don't want to talk about that at all.
People change.
I'm afraid of the rent.
I'm going to buy it soon. Wait.
I'll make a phone call.
I'm calling my boss.
Did you get a call?
Yes.
Show me.
I'm not here.
This is his house.
This is very spacious.
This is a good house.
It's different to make money.
This is amazing.
Did you put the camera in?
I put the camera in.
Is this okay?
I'm glad.
I did what I said.
But is this really okay?
Are you scared?
Don't be scared of the rent.
I'll take all the responsibility.
You just have to pay the rent.
You were aiming for the rent.
I'm sorry.
Wait.
I told you I had a magazine shoot today.
I'll be back soon.
Do it right.
I'll ask you.
You can make friends with me as an option.
I asked you.
See you.
Good luck.
Bye.
You are the manager.
I asked you to go to Aikanji first.
I have a meeting with a girl today.
I got the key.
I gave it to the manager.
Did you understand?
I'm scared.
I'm looking forward to it.
You are so mean to make me rape the manager.
Mean?
You'll be more relieved to know me.
I'm looking forward to it.
Cheers.
What?
Aika-chan, long time no see.
You look so young.
Do I?
Yes.
You look so young.
How did you get in?
What?
I came in.
Wait!
Let me go!
What?
Stop!
Wait!
What?
Don't touch me!
Stop!
No! No! No!
No!
Stop it!
I'm sorry.
Are you sad?
I'm a little sick.
I'm very sad.
I'm sorry.
Go home.
Are you sad?
Let me go.
I'm sorry.
Go home.
Are you okay?
You are noisy.
Yeah!
Oh, no!
I don't want to do this anymore.
You're a good girl.
You're living a good life.
No!
Oh, no!
Stop it!
I said it's not a scratch.
I said it's a scratch.
It's amazing.
Can't you hear anything?
This apartment is really nice.
You live in a nice place.
I'll call and ask what's going on.
Wait a minute.
I'm in pain.
You look very painful.
You are in a big trouble.
Are you okay?
I want you to cry.
I'll go to the hospital.
Wait for me.
Did you see that?
I'll go to the hospital.
Go.
I don't want to go to the hospital.
No!
What's wrong?
What is this place?
It's amazing!
Shut up!
Mao-san!
What's going on?
What's wrong?
Mao-san!
I think you're going to be in trouble!
Mao-san, help me!
Let me go!
What are you going to do if you get caught?
What was it?
What is this?
What are you doing?
Hey!
Let's record it.
We're going to make a memory.
Hey!
Mao-san!
Why?
I have to record this.
Don't take it.
I'm in trouble.
Stop it!
You're a bitch!
Mao-san, why are you recording?
This is also a bitch.
Stop it!
You look good.
You look the same as when you were a professional.
You're a bitch.
Show me your face.
Take a good picture of my face.
Do you remember when you were working?
You're getting too carried away.
I'll give you more.
Stop it!
What are you doing?
Are you embarrassed?
Don't take it.
You've been showing your manko to so many people.
Stop it!
Mao-san is the number one manko in Soap.
You're the number one manko in Soap.
Stop it!
How do you feel?
I feel good.
Stop it!
What's this?
Do you feel it?
You're crazy.
You're a bitch.
Stop it!
You're bleeding.
Mao-san!
Do you feel good?
Stop it!
Why are you doing this?
Do you feel good because I don't answer?
I'm asking you if you feel good or not.
I don't feel good.
You're lying.
I don't want to do it anymore.
You feel it, don't you?
You don't feel it, do you?
I don't feel it.
What do you think of this face?
You feel it, don't you?
I really feel it.
Do you feel it?
Stop it!
You're a bitch.
What do you think of this?
What was it?
Do you still want to date Aika?
What do you think of this?
Don't show me.
I'll show you.
You're cute.
Where are you going?
Wait.
I'm scared.
Don't be crazy.
You're too crazy.
Are you okay?
Did you get a cold?
Did you forget that you're a girl?
You got a lot of love from me, didn't you?
I'm going to make you cute again today.
Manager
Stop it.
Let go of me.
It's noisy.
It's a nuisance to your neighborhood.
What if you make such a loud voice and come to your neighborhood?
What are you going to do?
You'll be in trouble if you're seen.
Do you know that I'm a cleaning lady?
If you make a noise, I don't know what to do.
Do you understand?
Feel it.
Stop it.
It's noisy.
I'm sorry.
I'm glad I was a good girl.
It's nice to have a lot of cute kids.
Stop it.
Don't you want to be seen?
I'll hide your face.
Stop it.
You can't see my face, can you?
Do you want to feel good?
I'm cold.
You're wet.
You're not satisfied with your boyfriend's penis, are you?
You're a bitch.
What do you think?
Stop it.
I won't stop.
Wait.
Did you say it?
I didn't say it.
Then, I'll make you do it.
I'll make you do it more.
You don't have enough love.
Do you feel good?
What's wrong with your face?
You look like you're looking down on me.
You're annoying.
I know.
You should stop it.
You're not supposed to do it.
You're a bitch.
You bite me.
Apologize to me.
Take off your legs.
I don't want to.
Why do I have to take off my legs?
Your legs look good on you.
You look good with such a gorgeous underwear.
You're a bitch.
You're used to it.
Go away.
I don't want to.
I'm going to sleep.
You should be more obedient to her.
No!
Do you think you're a man?
You're going to be angry if you're the same woman.
You're not good enough.
Stop it!
Don't touch me!
You still have a beautiful face.
Stop it!
You seduced me with your body.
Turn around.
Stop it!
What's wrong?
Why are you so excited?
I'm sorry.
Turn around.
Where are you going?
No!
Go home!
Do you think you can run away?
Stop it!
Why are you trying to run away?
If you run away, this video will be spread.
When 1.3 million people watch this video, let's take a picture together.
No!
Let's show this to 1.3 million people.
I think we can get more followers.
You're more beautiful.
No!
You're so cute.
You look good in that face.
Let's show it to them.
No!
Why are you so excited?
You're pretending to go again.
You're a liar.
No!
You're pretending to go again.
It's not over yet.
Okay?
Let's stop it.
Stop it.
Hey!
No!
You're noisy.
Open your mouth.
Open it.
Don't bite me.
You were bitten.
That's why you were making that voice.
Do you know what will happen if you bite me?
1.3 million people may watch this video.
Bite me more.
You're so naive.
Can you bite me?
Go deeper.
Look at me.
You're so wet.
Is it painful?
It's not over yet.
Why are you trying to end it?
You're noisy.
Do you feel good?
I feel good.
You're making a weird face.
You're so naughty.
You wanted to run away, didn't you?
Did you wait for me?
What is this?
I've never seen such a thing.
You look terrible.
Look at you.
Is this OK?
Don't push me.
I can push you.
No.
You look terrible.
Look at you.
I've never seen such a thing.
Stop it.
I'm done.
You want to run away, don't you?
Where can you run away?
Stop it.
You'll get hurt if you get angry at me.
I'm fine.
Stop it!
Is Aika's mic closed?
I think so.
The manager said he wanted a baby.
I'll call him for you.
Stop it!
You have money, so you can raise two children.
I don't want to do that!
If you close the mic, the manager will cry.
Stop it!
I don't want to do that!
You are very desperate.
You are holding your head up.
Look at Aika.
You are feeling it.
You are feeling it with your head.
I don't want to do that.
You are holding your head up.
You can feel it with your head.
You can feel it, right?
No.
I don't want to do that.
You are holding your head up.
Can you feel it?
I'll give you a shock.
Yay!
Aika's pussy and the manager's penis are together.
Look at this.
You can see the hole in the butt.
Stop it!
This is the hole in the butt of a famous person.
You are shaking.
Stop it!
You smell like a woman.
Turn around.
You are kissing.
Open your mouth.
This is a silent attack.
You are gross.
Stop it!
Why?
Your back is shaking.
Are you sure?
You are lying, aren't you?
You are lying.
You are lying again.
You are not energetic enough.
Where are you going?
No!
Let me go home.
You are lying.
No!
What are you going to do?
I can't.
Do you want to go back to your colleagues?
Let's work together again.
I can't.
What are you going to do?
You are annoying.
Let me touch you more.
I'll eat you.
Stop it.
You are lying.
Your back is shaking.
How do you like this present?
Do you like it?
I'm tired.
Let me see.
Mom.
Tell me you are going to go.
I don't understand.
Will you stop me if I go?
I'll think about it.
Go ahead.
Go.
You can't even breathe as a woman.
I'll go.
Do you think this is true?
It's a lie.
Don't lie.
I'm a woman.
Stop it.
I'm glad you can't break it.
It's wet.
Stop it.
Do you get wet when you dance?
No?
You like me.
I'm glad.
Tell me.
You like me more than your boyfriend.
I've never liked you.
What are you talking about?
I can't.
Stop it.
I'm glad you feel better.
You feel better, don't you?
I'm glad.
You are lucky.
You said you would go when I go.
I'll go.
Go.
Don't stop me.
I'll go.
I'll be glad if you go.
Stop it.
Stop it!
I'm still young.
You...
Don't move.
You look like you like it the most.
You can do it.
Stop it.
Is it OK?
You said you like to be pushed from behind.
You are a bitch.
You are still young.
You said you wanted to go.
I don't know what you are talking about.
I can't hear you.
You are a bitch.
Oh, my God!
That's enough!
I don't think so.
You can enjoy it a lot.
She hasn't enjoyed it yet.
You should close the door more.
What?
Did you close the door too much?
I told you.
I told you it's over.
You didn't.
I told you.
You lied to me.
I didn't.
You haven't closed the door yet.
Do you want to close the door more?
I want you to enjoy it more.
I don't want to.
Do you want to go to the bathroom again?
Did you enjoy it so much?
I'll help you.
Stop it!
Don't stop me!
Hey, manager, come with me!
Ah, no!
I'm so tired when I'm running, I'm like...
I'm so scared, I'm going to lose my mind!
What's wrong?
Are you going to run away again?
With your manager's dick?
Look at that and tell me.
Look at this.
I can't say it!
I told you it wouldn't end if you didn't say it.
Hikaru...
Whose?
Whose dick?
Manager's...
I'm going.
Hikaru, Hikaru, Hikaru, Hikaru...
I can't believe it.
It's disgusting.
Be careful.
Can you see it?
This is the tent of your favorite owner.
No, no, no.
I'm going to go.
No.
Look at it carefully.
Manager!
What?
We're talking about something else.
I told you to put it in.
Why are you putting it in there?
I don't know.
Hurry up and put it in.
I'm done.
Put it in.
It's over.
I'm sorry.
Let's do it again.
Don't put it in.
Why?
I put it in.
It won't end until you put it in.
I told you.
I want a baby.
I don't know if it's a baby.
It's not moving.
That's right.
It's a baby.
It's not moving.
Squeeze it out.
It's a baby.
You want a baby, don't you?
I'm the manager's treasure.
Say you want a baby.
I'll make this video popular.
I want a baby.
Hurry up and move.
I'm telling you to move.
I can't.
You were doing better when you were a manager.
You can't do it anymore.
You can move, right?
I'll show you the real thing.
Otherwise, the manager...
You have to move.
You don't have to.
Is it okay?
Can I show you the picture of 130,000 people?
And your boyfriend?
Can I show you?
Then you know what I'm talking about.
Stop it.
Please stop it.
Do you want to feel it?
Or do you want something stronger?
Stop it.
I'll take your nipples.
Do you like this?
Stop it.
You're going to do it.
I can't.
Stop it.
I'm sorry.
Please put the manager's nipples in.
The video will be broadcast all over the world.
Say it.
Manager.
Manager, please put my nipples in.
Where?
Please put my nipples in.
Stop it.
No.
I'm gonna cry.
No!
I have to move alone.
Stop!
Are you okay?
Take a good picture.
I can't get in.
Help me!
How is it?
Are you happy?
Let's see.
You are so happy.
You took a lot of pictures.
Are you happy?
Take a picture of me.
Let's take a picture together.
Let's put them together.
You took a lot of pictures.
It was fun.
It's not over yet.
Let's take a break and continue.
I'm hungry.
I don't have anything.
Hey!
Cheers!
Look at this.
How long are you going to do this?
It's so good.
I'm not going to eat this. It's so good.
I'm so tired.
Manager.
How many times did you say that?
You said it too much.
Show me.
I'm a Norwegian.
I'm so excited that I can't breathe.
I'm glad you gave me a lot of pictures.
Show me your boyfriend's picture.
No.
Why? He's your friend.
Show me.
No?
Then you can spend time alone.
Show me.
It's your bag, isn't it?
Stop it.
Don't touch it.
This is it.
It's a picture of you and me.
You look so lovely.
What are you taking a picture of?
It's good.
I'm embarrassed.
Let's take a picture together.
What?
When are you going to meet me?
I'll see you when you're not wearing a coat.
I'm a manager.
You're young, but you're amazing.
You're a manager now, right?
But you're naked.
Stop it.
I don't want to.
I want to go to the bathroom.
What?
Manager.
Bring me a glass.
No.
Why?
You want to go to the bathroom, right?
I want to go to the bathroom.
Come here.
Please take it.
Hurry up.
You want me to do it here, right?
Do you want me to hold it in?
I can't use the bathroom.
I'll hold it in or do it here.
Hurry up.
I'm embarrassed.
I know you're not going to take a picture, so hurry up.
You're embarrassed because you're looking at me.
You can't hold it in, can you?
I'm holding it in.
You've been holding it in all this time.
You're wet.
Manager.
I can't hold it in.
Why?
You're wet, so wipe it off.
Do I have to wipe it off?
It's your mouth.
Hurry up.
No.
You can't do that.
I can't.
You are serious.
Oh, my god!
How does it taste?
Salty.
You are a good boy.
You are full of energy.
I'm not done yet.
You are inviting your friends after this, right?
Yes.
I don't like to be naked.
It's embarrassing.
And it's not good.
Wait a minute.
What's that?
I don't care.
Do you want to do it again?
No.
I don't care.
I'll take this.
Put this on.
Don't you wear it?
I don't care if you are naked.
It's embarrassing.
It's good.
You are a good boy.
Come on.
She really comes.
She's a great person.
You're always like that.
She's great.
She's really great.
She's so cute.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
I'm Aika.
Sit down.
You're so cute.
Go to the middle.
Today,
I'm going to play with you
as much as I want.
You can do whatever you want.
Really?
I want you to do it.
You're so cute.
She's always looking at you.
I'll kiss you.
Don't move.
You're so good at it.
Next, this way.
You're so cute.
Look at this.
This is Aika's underwear.
It looks good on you.
I'll show you.
It's so beautiful.
I can't close my legs.
I'll touch you.
Don't take it off.
I'm taking a lot of pictures.
Are you happy?
I'm happy.
Isn't it great?
I didn't take it off.
Show me your face.
Is it comfortable?
Which is more comfortable?
Which feels better?
Wait.
I don't want to wait.
You are getting bigger.
No!
Stop it!
You are closing it.
You like it.
Do you like it?
Say it.
You couldn't hear it.
Say it again.
Look at me.
Say you like it.
Say it.
You like it.
Oh, my gosh!
You are saying it.
You like it.
I like both.
Do you like it?
You like it.
What is that?
I want to hear it.
You are using it.
Stop it.
You used it a lot.
Did you use it a lot?
You are licking it.
You are licking it from the top of the panties.
Like this?
Stop it.
I didn't use it yet.
You can see it.
You like it, don't you?
You bitch.
You said you like it.
Your voice is leaking.
You are using it a lot.
Let me go.
No.
Where are you touching?
You are scratching your body.
You are disturbing me.
Wait.
Why are you acting like you are nice?
What?
When I go to you, you should say you will go.
So what?
Let's go.
No.
You are holding it.
You are going.
I'm going.
I'm going to take a lot of pictures.
You can see it.
Stop it.
You are using it a lot.
You are disturbing me.
I'm going to clean it.
You are happy.
How is it?
You are scratching your body.
You are using it a lot.
Wait.
What?
Say it.
I'm going.
Stop it.
You can't use it.
How is it?
Are you happy?
You wanted to go.
I don't think so.
Stop it.
You are so mean.
Are you sad?
You wanted to go.
How is it?
You can go if I say so.
Show me your erotic look.
Show me.
Put your knees on it.
What is this?
You were wearing this when you were active.
I'm going to make you stronger.
How is it?
Show me.
Don't wait.
How is it?
Stop it.
You wanted to go.
I'm going to make you stronger.
You can't.
Stop it.
You can't use it yet.
I'm going to make you stronger.
Your hips are moving.
Put your knees on it.
Stop it.
Show me your erotic look.
You are going to run away.
You are so angry.
Stop it.
What is that look?
Don't stare at me.
What?
You want to go?
How is it?
You can go if I say so.
I'm going.
What?
I can't hear you.
I want to hear you.
I don't want to say it.
You are going to get angry if you keep making that face.
Hurry up.
How is it?
I want to go.
You want to go.
You two make her go.
I don't want to go.
You are a pervert.
Stop it.
Don't take it.
You are so cute.
I put her in the bed earlier.
She was feeling inside.
You love the bed, don't you?
You are not good at it.
You should attack her inside.
You were good at it.
I was not.
You put her in the bed earlier.
Do you want to sleep?
You don't want to?
Do you want to stay here?
You should make her wet.
Good girl.
You are cute.
You were wet.
You are still dry.
You should put her in the bed.
You should make her wet.
You are still wet.
More.
You are so cute.
You should make her wet.
You are cute.
You are dirty.
You are wet.
What do you want to do?
Do you want to be attacked?
You can sleep.
You wanted to be attacked.
You are so cute.
You are attacked.
Stop it.
Look at her.
Don't put her in the bed.
You are so cute.
You can't move her.
You are so wet.
You are beautiful.
You are so cute.
You like to be attacked.
Stop it.
You are so wet.
No.
Stop it.
You can't move her.
I don't want to cry.
No.
This is amazing.
I'll do it.
I'm not in a good mood.
What is this?
What is this? Tell me.
What is this feeling?
I've never experienced this.
What is this?
Stop it.
Tell me.
I feel something.
This is...
Be more violent.
I'm not in a good mood.
Stop it.
This is amazing.
I'll do it.
I'm in a good mood.
Stop it.
Which one is bigger?
You said you won't let go of me.
Help me.
I'll cry.
No.
You like to live forever, don't you?
Don't say that!
You don't have a pain, do you?
Hey, let me read your face.
Don't move.
Manager, put this in.
Let me read your face.
Do you think this will work?
It may be a little too much.
Because you don't react well.
That's not true.
I only say no.
Then, put this in.
What should I do?
It may be great if you drink from here.
I'm sorry.
Here we go.
One, two.
Oh my god!
It smells so good!
It's not enough, manager!
More!
To our friendship!
Cheers!
No!
Shake it!
Oh my god!
Do you want to look at me?
No!
Ready?
If you drink this much, you'll get sick.
You want to drink, don't you?
I want to drink.
I'll drink.
Drink.
It's delicious.
Is it your first experience?
Yes.
Don't say, stop it.
Do you understand?
Look at this mouth.
Look at this.
What's in front of you?
You didn't have enough alcohol?
I want to drink.
You want to drink, don't you?
I want to touch you.
Don't touch me.
You don't have enough alcohol?
I'll do it again if you don't do it properly.
You should drink it properly.
Is it delicious?
Look at the camera.
I'm getting sick.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Don't do that.
I want to drink.
I'm sick.
You didn't say you wanted to drink.
I said.
You should lick it properly.
It's the best.
You're getting bigger.
You're good at licking.
You're a soap woman.
You should lick us.
I'm going to sleep.
I'm getting sick.
You should do it properly.
You know what's in the video, don't you?
I'm sure you all want to see it.
You're a soap woman.
You're a good girl.
Did you spit it out?
You're eating with a manko.
Aika's manko.
I'm going to do it now.
Go.
You're a good girl.
Don't let go of me.
Put it deeper.
You're eating with a manko.
You're a pervert.
You can give it back to me.
Why are you trying to run away?
I don't know what you're talking about.
Who said you could let go of me?
I'm going to do it.
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
You look comfortable.
Thank you.
You made me feel good.
No.
I can't drink it.
Do you smell it?
The room smells good.
I'm tired.
I'm also comfortable.
Did you like it?
What do you do?
I can't stand it anymore.
You want it, don't you?
It's long.
You put it out too much.
No.
Open your mouth.
It smells good.
Don't put it out.
I can't drink it.
What's wrong with you?
I told you to drink it.
Why?
It's disgusting.
You don't want this anymore, do you?
You want the real thing, don't you?
Come on, get up.
You want the real thing now, don't you?
No, I don't.
Look, you didn't do it earlier.
Move.
What?
No, I'm fine.
You can't do that.
You almost moved when I put you on the bed.
No, I don't want to.
Come on.
Move.
What?
If you don't move, the manager will be angry.
I can't move.
Why?
Did you get your back out of the bed?
Yes.
Because you feel good?
No.
Stop it.
I'll look at you.
You have a mark.
Look at me.
You look like a flying squirrel.
Come on, put your face to me.
Yay.
This is Aika's friend.
Say cheese.
Come on.
Yay.
Aika is putting her tail on me.
You are the best.
No, no, no.
You did it!
What's your name?
Kouta
You lost to Kouta?
Is that okay?
I want you to get a lot of them
What are you doing?
I'm gonna do it.
You should do it over there.
Stop it.
Over here.
I'm gonna do it.
No!
No...
Oh, no...
Try it.
Look at your face.
You look like a cat.
You look like a big cat.
No!
Look at me.
You look like a cat.
Oh, no!
Don't stop it.
You look like a big cat.
I'm getting excited.
No!
How do you feel now?
Oh, no!
I'm so happy that you're happy.
You look like a big cat.
Oh, no!
Open your eyes.
You can see it, right?
Oh, no!
Who's crying?
Do you feel good?
You should admit it.
Then, everyone will do their best.
Look!
You must feel good.
Hey!
Don't pretend to be innocent.
You're a bitch.
Oh, no!
I can't do it anymore.
It's so tight.
I'm so bored.
I can't do it.
Do it yourself.
It's a pain in the ass.
You can do it.
I can't do it.
It's so painful.
It's in my mouth.
Look at me.
I'm a human.
Which one do you like better?
Which one?
I'm going to have to get a doctor to do it.
It's so hard.
It's so easy.
You're breathing heavily again.
Which one do you like better?
You don't like it?
Why?
You said it.
Let's ask him again.
Which one do you like better?
Your boyfriend or Ten-chan?
Ten-chan.
I did it!
How do you feel?
It's great!
I feel great!
I can't hear you.
I'm really happy.
I feel great!
No, no, no!
It's coming!
I'll put this in, too.
Really?
I got it.
No, no, no!
It's coming!
Oh, no!
No, no, no!
It's heavy.
It hurts.
It stinks!
What a waste!
It's all out.
It's a waste, so put it in.
It's a waste.
I don't want to.
I'll put it all in.
It's a mess.
You're a bitch.
I'll put it in.
You can put it in.
No!
I'll put it in.
Look, look.
It's all white.
It's all wrinkled because of the manager.
Are you happy?
Look at this.
It's all wrinkled, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
Oh, my.
There are so many spiders.
It's so cool.
It's all white.
It's a picture of a man who is having sex with a man who is a sexy girl.
Take a good picture of it.
It's all wrinkled.
It's all white.
I can't do it anymore.
What are you talking about?
What will happen?
I want to see it.
What will happen if I do it more?
What will happen?
I want to see it.
I can't do it.
I'm so happy.
Are you going to be weird?
Move yourself.
You can move, right?
I'm so happy.
I heard that Aiko's drawing is amazing.
I want to see it.
Is it like this?
Show me more.
I'm so happy.
Do you feel good?
You can move more.
No, no, no.
You're going to be weird.
I can't stand it anymore.
Where do you want it?
Tell me.
Tell me where you want it.
Where do you want it?
Tell me quickly.
I can't stand it anymore.
I'm so glad you gave me so much.
I'm so glad you came back to the beach.
Is it okay to give me so much?
I'm so full.
Oh, no. You gave her so much.
You're so excited.
I'm going to pay for this.
That's great.
That's good.
Hey, the store is closed today.
Let's go.
Really?
Isn't it bad?
Yes.
Okay.
I'll do my best.
See you.
She is the best owner.
I don't think I can do this.
I don't think so.
You were very excited.
I can't.
I was surprised that you didn't make too much noise.
You can hear it.
You're a baby.
You're late! I finally got here!
Sorry!
What were you doing?
I was just picking up girls.
You're the worst!
My friend is here!
You were lonely after the manager left.
It's real!
Super famous influencer!
You noticed?
I did.
You're so chubby!
You noticed?
What's with that outfit?
Let's get closer.
Let's toast!
Hold this.
To our wonderful meeting today!
Really?
Nice to meet you!
To our wonderful meeting today!
Cheers!
It's so good!
Look at my Aika!
What?
You're not being nice.
I'm going to get more love from you.
So you should be nicer.
You can't say hi to me.
Mao.
Do you want to see me being a pervert?
You want to see me, right?
I do!
Why are you showing me?
You're just jealous of me.
What?
I'm a successful soap actress.
You're still a soap actress.
What are you talking about?
You're crazy.
You're jealous of me.
You're crazy!
Is that all you want to say?
I'll show you my pervert side.
You're satisfied with that, right?
You're so motivated.
What?
Hey!
You're so aggressive.
You want to see this?
Can you do that?
You're so aggressive.
My arm hurts.
You wanted to see this?
It feels good.
It's hot.
You're so erotic.
More.
I want to see your pervert side.
Really?
You're so erotic.
You're so different from before.
You're so good.
Do you like erotic people?
I like them.
You're so good.
Do you like that?
I love you.
You're so good.
I want you to do more.
I love you.
You're so good.
You want me to do that?
I want to do that.
Can I do that?
I'll do it slowly.
Is it painful?
It's so hot.
You wanted to see my pervert side, right?
It's good.
It's so hot.
It's good, right?
I can do that.
You're so good.
You want me to do that?
You can't.
You want me to do that, right?
You're so good.
I like your face when you're angry.
It's not in there.
You can't do that yet.
You can do that.
You're the best, right?
You hit me.
You're so good.
It's fun.
I'm getting scared.
I want more.
You want more?
You're so good.
Can I touch you?
More.
More?
It's so good.
You can't.
Come here.
Your face.
You're so good.
I'll show you my sexiness.
You'll like me more.
You'll show me your sexiness, right?
Show me.
You can't.
Look.
You're already on my face.
I'm relieved.
My 130,000 followers.
She's crazy.
Good evening.
Watch me getting sexy.
What's wrong?
Are you okay?
I have to show you more.
I can't see you.
You can't see me?
Inside?
You have a lot of pimples.
Are you okay?
I can see you.
You're crazy.
More.
I'll do it.
I feel so good!
I'm going to go.
Babu, she's going to live for 130,000 years.
This guy.
I'm so happy.
I'm going crazy.
I want a baby.
Are you sure?
I'm sure.
I got a baby.
I'm so happy.
I want to do more live streaming.
I'm going to go.
It's so sour.
I'm going to drink this water.
That's great.
It's hitting my throat.
You're doing it yourself?
It feels good.
I'm so happy.
I can't do live streaming.
My followers want to see this.
If you want to see it, show me what you want to see.
I'm so happy.
Which one do you want to put in?
I don't know.
I'll put in here.
Really?
I want to go behind you.
I don't want to.
I'm going to put it in here.
Oh no, oh no, I'm gonna climax.
I'm gonna climax.
It's so narrow.
Mao-san, are you jealous of me?
No way.
You're crazy.
I've been streaming for 130,000 years.
Oh no, oh no, I'm gonna climax.
There are people who are jealous of me because I'm comfortable.
Of course.
More?
More.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
I'm gonna climax.
Oh no, oh no, oh no.
It feels good.
I'm gonna climax.
Don't climax.
You're streaming live.
You're so jealous.
I'm gonna climax.
Mom, you can't do that.
I want to go to the bathroom.
Sit down.
Put it in.
I'm gonna climax.
It's so hard.
It feels good.
Why are you moving?
Of course.
I'm gonna climax.
You're crazy.
Why are you stopping?
Don't stop.
I'm gonna climax.
There.
I'm so sorry.
You don't like this, do you?
One more time.
There are so many people watching us.
They are watching us.
I'm so happy.
Please lick me more.
How do you like my butt?
It's the best.
I'm so happy.
Please put your tongue out.
It's amazing.
That's amazing.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
I'm so sorry.
I want to go.
My mouth feels weird.
I'm sorry.
I'm scared from here.
Oh, my God.
I told you to be quiet.
I'll put it here.
Lick it.
I'm so scared.
Oh, my God.
Pussy is soaked.
Was she like this?
She's having a lot of fun.
I'm kind of pissed off.
It's so good!
Don't stop me!
It's good!
I can't stop!
I'm so happy!
Does it feel good, Mao?
It feels good!
It feels good to the point that I feel like I'm going to climax.
Mao, did you climax again?
Mao is not coming out.
Don't do it!
It's so tight!
Feels good!
My legs hurt.
Oh, no.
I think it's almost time.
What's wrong?
I'm happy.
Wait a minute.
Let's go over there.
Where are you?
Here?
Come here.
I'm here.
Look at me.
Do you know who I am?
Your girlfriend was actually this bitch.
Are you happy?
Poor girl.
It hurts.
I feel good now.
You're crazy.
Let's have fun over there.
Don't stop me.
No.
I'm going home.
I'm so happy.
Look at me.
This is who I am.
I feel good.
I'm so happy.
Wow! You are so strong!
Do you have such a hobby?
Are you a pervert?
Are you a pervert couple?
You are getting stronger.
Look!
Your boyfriend was a pervert.
He is excited to see his girlfriend taking a video of him.
Do you feel good?
What do you mean?
Which do you feel good? Aika or me?
This is the best of Aika's boyfriend.
You are a bad girl.
Which do you like?
Tell me.
It doesn't matter.
Which do you like?
Tell me.
You are getting stronger.
Aika, look!
She was watching.
Look!
Look! Aika is being attacked.
Her boyfriend is being a pervert.
Are you serious?
Can I touch you?
Can I?
Oh, my!
I can't see.
Let me see.
Aika!
You are getting stronger.
Let me see your lips.
It feels good.
I've never seen such a good baby.
Aika, look closer.
Bring it here.
I can't see.
It's amazing.
I'm so hungry. Can you see?
How do you feel?
Are you frustrated?
It feels good.
I might go to Aika's husband's house.
No, no, no.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
I'm so happy.
I'm going to go.
It's amazing.
It's a baby.
How do you feel?
Do you feel the same as me?
It's amazing.
You're so funny.
My microphone feels good.
I'm glad.
It feels better than your microphone.
My microphone feels good, too.
Don't move.
It feels good.
No, no, no.
I'm going.
I can't stop.
Look at this.
She is having sex with a man.
She is a psychopath.
I'm so happy.
Look at this.
Isn't it incredible?
She was so surprised to see me.
I didn't expect that.
That's true.
She is so comfortable.
You are excited to see my face.
That's true.
I hate Aika.
I'm wet.
Are you going to make me wet again?
I'm sorry.
It's the best.
It feels good.
I'm annoyed.
It's really annoying.
I can't stand it.
I'm sorry.
I'll give you a lot.
Give me a lot.
It hurts.
Look at this.
It's a lot.
There's a lot of it.
I'm so happy.
Did you see it?
Did you wait for me?
I'm getting more and more white.
Look at this.
It feels good.
I didn't know it was this much.
I didn't know.
What are you doing?
It's the best.
I'm so happy.
You like a bitch, don't you?
It's the best.
I'm so happy.
It feels good.
I can't stand it.
Don't wake me up.
You are a pervert.
You lick my bun.
It's easy for you.
I can't be with you.
Which one do you like?
You can't be without me.
Let me taste you.
You are dirty.
I'll clean you up.
Why are you so soft?
Let me in.
Why don't you let me in?
Don't you like it?
Tell me to let you in.
Tell me that you want me.
Can't you say it?
I want you.
One more time.
You want me.
Do you want me?
Come here.
It feels good.
It feels good just to be in here.
You are so soft.
I knew it.
Let's take a picture.
It feels good.
I'm so good.
It feels good just to be here.
What should I do?
Nnnnnnnnnn...
Good...
Why am I already resting?
What a waste...
Oh my god!
It's like a blue sky.
I'm so sleepy.
You're still sleepy?
What's wrong?
I'm going to sleep.
Oh no!
It feels so good.
I'm so sleepy.
I'm glad you can use the phrase
that you used with Kanae.
Let me go! Let me go!
You have a lot of hair!
I'll squeeze it for you.
But you can't take it off, can you?
I want you to take it off.
Please.
Please!
Oh, my God!
I'll take it off.
Please!
I'm happy.
Look at this.
You have a lot of hair.
You just took it off.
Look at this.
It stinks.
What? It stinks?
Don't say that.
It stinks.
Are you still in a bad mood?
I feel good.
You look embarrassed.
Aren't you embarrassed to be looked at like this?
I'm happy.
I'll take it off, too.
I'll take it off again.
It's flying.
It's so funny.
I'm full of hair.
How many times did you take it off?
I know.
Why are you still in a bad mood?
You're so funny.
I can't take it off yet.
You're still in a bad mood, aren't you?
I can't take it off.
Oh, my God!
I can't believe I can love you.
I feel good.
I'm a woman of this kind.
Can you give it to me?
I can't.
Help me.
Give it to me.
I'll give it to you.
I can't.
I feel good.
I'm a woman of this kind.
Help me.
I can't.
I'm really taking it off.
You're a pervert.
I can't.
Stop it.
I can't take it off.
It's bitter.
My boyfriend is a pervert.
I can't.
There are a lot of things in me.
You are such a bitch.
You are a psychopath.
But you are with me.
So, please look forward to the next one.
What?
I will prepare a lot of them.
What are you talking about?