I'm going to drink champagne.
Isn't it great?
I'll put this in.
It looks very tasty.
It looks really good.
cheers!
Let's eat.
This is good.
I am going to eat now.
what is it?
Is it a gift?
I'm so happy.
Thanks.
chocolate?
It looks very tasty.
What's this?
So cute.
Thanks.
I am very happy.
I am so embarrassed.
I feel awkward being around ghosts.
That is not true.
Amazing.
It's very cute.
So cute.
Is it a brand?
I've seen it before.
It's a very expensive one.
did you buy it?
I received this as a gift.
I am her boyfriend.
I have a boyfriend.
I understand.
he treats me well.
He is a very expensive man.
He is a venture capitalist.
Venture capitalist?
Is he a company?
He is a company.
He is the president.
He is great.
cheers!
This is good.
I'm happy with an afternoon drink.
Why drink a light bar in the afternoon?
I have something to say.
Oh, you brought a camera.
I brought it.
very heavy.
sorry.
It seems to be recording.
Is it a recording?
Yes.
I'm watered down by customers.
I hear I'm a famous influencer now.
I ran into this guy the other day.
look at this.
look.
It looks very tasty.
This is where?
I went from Matma to a restaurant in a luxury hotel.
I'm taking pictures all the time.
They have a difference.
It's too fancy.
It used to be simpler.
This is a port girl.
Yes.
I don't know because I'm fat.
I've been touching my phone.
How many likes did you get?
I have no idea.
130,000 people.
Did you hear it?
What?
130,000 people.
It's interesting.
Aika is like this now.
We talked about soap.
She hated it instantly.
I think that's how it is in the video.
look at this.
I met the manager.
I recently went to a restaurant.
I met Eka.
I said I want to go there.
Do you remember the izakaya near the restaurant?
a bit old.
Did you see her face?
She said she didn't want to talk anymore.
let's go there.
This is a great time.
Do you remember the waiting room where Aixiang was?
I decorated the waiting room.
There were no girls in the waiting room.
You are laughing at me.
I'm not kidding you.
I'm laughing at you.
It was fun drinking with everyone.
This is who I am.
I don't want to talk about the old days.
I'm still doing it.
I feel rejected.
I am very sad.
I am angry.
I'm a little annoyed.
But the world we live in is different.
what is she doing?
She has a young manager boyfriend.
She has no money.
She eats well and drinks well.
I envy her very much.
I am angry.
I'm thinking about one thing.
what is it?
I'm thinking about raping Aika.
rape?
I do not understand.
I am angry.
I'm thinking about raping Aika.
I'm terrified of making my old friend angry.
You want to see it too.
I am going to hell.
sorry.
You are wonderful.
You look happy.
let's go.
I'm going.
I'm back.
Welcome back.
what have you done?
You're back.
Congratulations.
What's this?
I am leaving.
I’m waiting for you.
Congratulations.
Happy birthday to you
happy birthday dear aikawa
I did it!
do it again!
I gotta go
Congratulations! Thank you!
I'm so happy!
Thank you!
Aikawa, today's work must be very tiring
I'm so happy! I am very tired
I thought you'd be fine
I'm so happy!
i will do my best
Let's do our best!
By the way, we'll be back early tomorrow
Really?
Don't drink until then!
i will be drunk
We used to use our bodies to make money.
But right now, I don't want to talk about that at all.
People change.
I'm afraid of rent.
I will be buying it soon. wait.
I will call.
I'm calling my boss.
Did you get the call?
Yes.
show me.
I'm not here.
This is his house.
It's very spacious.
This is a nice house.
Making money is different.
That's pretty amazing.
Did you put your camera in it?
I put the camera in.
Is this ok?
I am very happy.
I did as I was told.
But is it really good?
Are you afraid?
Don't be afraid of rent.
I will take all responsibility.
You only need to pay the rent.
Your goal is to rent.
sorry.
wait.
I told you I was shooting a magazine today.
I will be back soon.
Do it right.
I will ask you.
You can choose to befriend me.
I asked you.
goodbye.
Good luck.
You are the manager.
I'll let you go to the Aihan Temple first.
Today I'm going to meet a girl.
I got the key.
I gave it to the manager.
Do you understand it?
I am afraid.
I look forward to it.
You are so mean to make me rape the manager.
meaning is?
You will be more at ease knowing me.
I look forward to it.
cheers.
What?
Aika-chan, long time no see.
You look so young.
Am I?
Yes.
You look so young.
how did you get in
What?
I'm in.
wait!
Let me go!
What?
stop!
wait!
What?
Do not touch me!
stop!
No! No! No!
No!
stop!
sorry.
are you sad
I'm a little sick.
I am very depressed.
sorry.
go home.
are you sad
Let me go.
sorry.
go home.
How are you?
You are noisy.
Yes!
Oh no!
I don't want to do it again.
You are a good girl.
You live a good life.
No!
Oh no!
stop!
I say it's not a scratch.
I say it's scratches.
Amazing.
Can't you hear something?
This apartment is really nice.
You live in a nice place.
I'll call and find out what happened.
Wait a moment.
I'm in pain.
You look miserable.
You are in big trouble.
How are you?
i want you to cry.
I will go to the hospital.
wait for me.
Did you see it?
I will go to the hospital.
go.
I don't want to go to the hospital.
No!
What's wrong?
What is this place?
Amazing!
shut up!
Mao San!
what is going on?
What's wrong?
Mao San!
I think you're going to be in trouble!
Mao Saburo, help me!
Let me go!
What would you do if you got caught?
how was it before
What's this?
What are you doing?
Hey!
Let's record it.
We want to make a memory.
Hey!
Mao San!
Why?
I have to put this on the record.
Don't accept it.
I'm in trouble.
stop!
You are a whore!
Mao San, why are you recording?
It's also a bitch.
stop!
You look fine.
You look the same as you did in your career.
You are a bitch.
let me see your face.
Take a good picture of my face.
Do you remember when you were working?
You are so carried away.
I will give you more.
stop!
What are you doing?
are you embarrassed
Don't accept it.
You have shown your manko to many people.
stop!
Mao San is the No. 1 manco in the soap opera.
You're the #1 manko in a soap opera.
stop!
how do you feel?
I feel good.
stop!
What's this?
Did you feel it?
You are crazy.
You are a bitch.
stop!
You are bleeding.
Mao San!
how are you feeling
stop!
why are you doing this
Because I don't answer do you feel good?
I ask you how you feel.
I do not feel well.
you are lying.
I don't want to do it again.
You feel it, don't you?
You don't feel it, do you?
I don't feel it.
What do you think of this face?
You feel it, don't you?
I really feel it.
Did you feel it?
stop!
You are a bitch.
What do you think of this?
how was it before
Do you still want to date Eka?
What do you think of this?
Don't show me.
I show you.
you are cute.
where are you going?
wait.
I am afraid.
Don't be crazy.
You are crazy.
How are you?
Are you sick?
Did you forget you're a girl?
You get a lot of love from me, don't you?
Today I'm going to make you cute again.
manager
stop.
Let me go.
very noisy.
This can cause problems for your neighbors.
What if you yelled loudly into your neighborhood?
what are you going to do?
If you are seen you will be in trouble.
Did you know I'm a cleaning lady?
I don't know what to do if you make noise.
do you understand?
Feel it.
stop.
very noisy.
sorry.
I'm glad I'm a good girl.
It's great to have so many lovely kids.
stop.
Don't you want to be seen?
I will cover your face.
stop.
You can't see my face, can you?
Do you want to feel good?
I am cold.
You are soaked.
You're not happy with your boyfriend's penis, are you?
You are a bitch.
what do you think?
stop.
I will not stop.
wait.
Did you say it?
I did not say.
Well, I'll let you do it.
I will let you do more.
You don't have enough love.
how are you feeling
what happened to your face
You look like you're looking down on me.
you are annoying.
I know.
You should stop it.
You should not do this.
You are a bitch.
you bite me.
Apologize to me.
Get your legs off.
I do not want.
Why do I have to take my legs off?
Your legs look fine.
You look so good in such beautiful lingerie.
You are a bitch.
You are used to it.
leave.
I do not want.
I'm going to sleep.
You should be more submissive to her.
No!
Do you think you are a man?
If you are the same woman, you will be angry.
You are not good enough.
stop!
Do not touch me!
You still have a beautiful face.
stop!
You seduced me with your body.
turn around.
stop!
What's wrong?
why are you so excited
sorry.
turn around.
where are you going?
No!
go home!
Do you think you can escape?
stop!
why are you trying to escape
If you escape, this video will go viral.
Let's take a photo together as 1.3 million people watch this video.
No!
Let's show this to 1.3 million people.
I think we can get more followers.
You are more beautiful.
No!
you are so cute.
Your face looks good.
Let's show them.
No!
why are you so excited
You pretended to leave again.
You are a liar.
No!
You pretended to leave again.
It's not over yet.
OK?
Let's stop it.
stop.
Hey!
No!
You are noisy.
open mouth.
Open it.
don't bite me.
You are bitten.
That's why you make that sound.
Do you know what will happen if you bite me?
This video may have been viewed by 1.3 million people.
bite me again
you are too naive.
can you bite me
deeper.
look at me.
You are so wet.
Does it hurt?
It's not over yet.
Why are you trying to end it?
You are noisy.
how are you feeling
I feel good.
Your expression is very strange.
You are so naughty.
You want to run away, don't you?
Are you waiting for me?
What's this?
I've never seen anything like it.
You look bad.
looking at you.
Is this ok?
Don't push me.
I can push you.
No.
You look bad.
looking at you.
I've never seen anything like it.
stop.
I'm done.
You want to run away, don't you?
Where can you escape to?
stop.
If you get mad at me, you'll get hurt.
I'm fine.
stop!
Is Aika's microphone turned off?
I think so.
The manager said he wanted a baby.
I'll call him for you.
stop!
You are rich and can support two children.
I don't want to do that!
If you turn off the microphone, the manager will cry.
stop!
I don't want to do that!
You are desperate.
You look up.
Just look at Aika.
You are feeling it.
You feel it with your head.
I don't want to do that.
You look up.
You can feel it with your head.
You can feel it, right?
No.
I don't want to do that.
You look up.
can you feel it
I will give you a shock.
yeah!
Aika's pussy is with the manager's cock.
look at this.
You can see the hole in the ass.
stop!
This is the hole in the ass of celebrities.
You are shaking.
stop!
You smell like a woman.
turn around.
You are kissing.
open mouth.
This is a silent attack.
You are so disgusting.
stop!
Why?
Your back is shaking.
are you sure?
you're lying, aren't you?
you are lying.
You are lying again.
You don't have enough energy.
where are you going?
No!
let me go home.
you are lying.
No!
what are you going to do?
I can not.
Do you want to get back to your colleagues?
Let's work together again.
I can not.
what are you going to do?
you are annoying.
Let me touch you more.
I will eat you.
stop.
you are lying.
Your back is shaking.
What do you think of this gift?
do you like it
I'm tired.
let me see.
Mother.
tell me you're going.
I do not understand.
Will you stop me if I go?
I will think about it.
go ahead.
go.
As a woman, you can't even breathe.
I gotta go.
Do you think this is true?
This is a lie.
don't lie.
I am a woman.
stop.
I'm glad you couldn't break it.
It's wet.
stop.
Do you get wet when you dance?
No?
you like me.
I am very happy.
tell me.
You like me more than your boyfriend.
I never liked you.
what are you saying?
I can not.
stop.
I'm glad you're feeling better.
You feel better, don't you?
I am very happy.
You are in luck.
When you say I leave, you also leave.
I gotta go.
go.
don't stop me.
I gotta go.
I'd be happy if you went.
stop.
stop!
I am still young.
you...
Do not move.
It seems that you are the favorite.
You can do it.
stop.
May I?
You said you liked being pushed from behind.
You are a bitch.
You are still very young.
You say you want to go.
I do not know what you're talking about.
I can not hear you.
You are a bitch.
OMG!
enough!
I do not think so.
You can enjoy a lot.
She hasn't enjoyed it yet.
You should close the door more often.
What?
Are you closing the door too tightly?
I told you.
I told you it was over.
you have not.
I told you.
you lied to me.
I don't.
You haven't closed the door yet.
Would you like to close the door even tighter?
I want you to enjoy it more.
I do not want.
Do you still want to go to the bathroom again?
Do you enjoy it so much?
I will help you.
stop!
don't stop me!
Hey manager, come with me!
Oh no!
When I run I'm tired and I'm like...
I'm so scared, I'm about to lose my mind!
What's wrong?
Are you running away again?
With your manager's cock?
Check that out and tell me.
look at this.
I can't tell!
I told you, if you don't talk, it won't end.
Light...
who?
whose dick?
Manager's...
I'm going.
Light, light, light, light...
I can not believe it.
too disgusting.
be careful.
can you see it
This is your favorite host tent.
No no no.
I gotta go.
No.
look carefully.
manager!
What?
We are talking about other things.
I told you to put it in.
why did you put it there?
I have no idea.
Put it in now.
I'm done.
put it in.
it's over.
sorry.
Let's do it again.
Don't put it in.
Why?
I put it in.
It's not over until you put it in.
I told you.
I want a child.
I don't know if it's a baby.
It doesn't move.
That's right.
It's a baby.
It doesn't move.
squeeze it out.
It's a baby.
You want a baby, don't you?
I'm the manager's baby.
Say you want a baby.
I will make this video popular.
I want a child.
Hurry up.
I tell you to move.
I can not.
When you're a manager, you do it better.
You can't do this anymore.
You can move, right?
I will tell you the real thing.
Otherwise the manager...
You must move.
you should not.
May I?
Can I show you pictures of 130,000 people?
with your boyfriend?
can i show you
Then you know what I'm talking about.
stop.
Please stop.
Do you want to feel it?
Or do you want something stronger?
stop.
I will take your tits.
How do you like it?
stop.
You will.
I can not.
stop.
sorry.
Please put the manager's nipples in.
The video will be played around the world.
Speak.
manager.
Manager, please put my nipples in.
Where?
Please put my nipples in.
stop.
No.
I'm going to cry.
No!
I must act alone.
stop!
How are you?
Take a good photo.
I can not get in
help me!
how?
are you happy?
let's see.
you are so happy.
You take a lot of photos.
are you happy?
Take a picture of me.
Let's take a picture together.
Let's put it all together.
You take a lot of photos.
fun.
It's not over yet.
Let's take a break and move on.
I'm hungry.
I have nothing.
Hey!
cheers!
look at this.
How long are you going to do this?
It's amazing.
I am not going to eat this. It's amazing.
I am very tired.
manager.
How many times have you said this sentence?
You talk too much.
show me.
I am Norwegian.
I couldn't breathe with excitement.
I'm so glad you gave me lots of photos.
Show me a picture of your boyfriend.
No.
Why? He is your friend.
show me.
No?
Then you can be alone.
show me.
This is your bag, isn't it?
stop.
don't touch it.
This is it.
This is a picture of you and me.
You look so cute.
What are you taking pictures of?
This is good.
I am so embarrassed.
Let's take a picture together.
What?
When are you coming to see me?
I'll see you when you're not wearing your coat.
I am a manager.
You are young, but you are amazing.
You are the manager now, right?
But you are naked.
stop.
I do not want.
I want to go to the bathroom.
What?
manager.
give me a drink.
No.
Why?
You want to go to the bathroom, right?
I want to go to the bathroom.
come over.
Please take it.
hurry up.
You want me to do it here, right?
Do you want me to hide it?
I can't use the bathroom.
I'll keep it or do it here.
hurry up.
I am so embarrassed.
I know you can't take pictures, so hurry up.
You are embarrassed by looking at me.
You can't hold on, can you?
I keep it to myself.
You have been holding on all this time.
You are soaked.
manager.
I can't hold it anymore
Why?
You're wet, so wipe it off.
do i have to wipe it off?
This is your mouth.
hurry up.
No.
You can't do that.
I can not.
are you serious.
OMG!
How does it taste?
salty.
You are a good boy.
You are full of energy.
I'm not done yet.
Afterwards you invite your friends, right?
Yes.
I don't like nudity.
It's embarrassing.
This is not good.
Wait a moment.
what is that?
I do not care.
Do you want to do it again?
No.
I do not care.
I will take this.
wear this.
don't you wear it
I don't care if you're naked or not.
It's embarrassing.
This is good.
You are a good boy.
hurry up.
She really came.
She is a wonderful person.
you are always like this.
She is great.
She is really good.
she is so cute.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
I'm Aika.
sit down.
you are so cute.
go to the middle.
today,
I'll play with you all I want.
You can do whatever you want.
Really?
I want you to do this.
you are so cute.
She always looks at you.
I will kiss you.
Do not move.
You are so good at it.
Next, go this way.
you are so cute.
look at this.
This is Aika's underwear.
You look good in it.
I show you.
it is so beautiful.
I can't close my legs.
i will touch you.
Don't take it off.
I'm taking a lot of pictures.
are you happy?
I am very happy.
Isn't it great?
I didn't take it off.
let me see your face.
Comfortable?
Which is more comfortable?
Which feels better?
wait.
I don't want to wait.
You are getting bigger and bigger.
No!
stop!
You are closing it.
you like it.
do you like it
Speak.
you can't hear.
Say it again.
look at me.
Say you like it.
Speak.
you like it.
God!
you are right.
you like it.
I like both.
do you like it
you like it.
what is that?
I want to hear it.
you are using it.
stop.
You use it many times.
Do you use it a lot?
You are licking it.
You lick it from the top of your panties.
like this?
stop.
I haven't used it yet.
you can see.
you like it, don't you?
you bastard.
You say you like it.
Your voice is missing.
You use it a lot.
Let me go.
No.
Where are you touching?
You are scratching your body.
You are bothering me.
wait.
Why are you acting like a nice guy?
What?
When I go to you, you should say you will go.
so what?
let's go.
No.
you take it.
you are leaving.
I'm going.
I'm going to take a lot of pictures.
you can see.
stop.
You use it a lot.
You are bothering me.
I'm going to clean it up.
You are very happy.
how?
You are scratching your body.
You use it a lot.
wait.
What?
Speak.
I'm going.
stop.
You can't use it.
how?
are you happy?
You want to go.
I do not think so.
stop.
You are so mean.
are you sad
You want to go.
how?
If I say so you can go.
Show me your erotic expressions.
show me.
Put your knees on top.
What's this?
You wear this when you are active.
I will make you stronger.
how?
show me.
don't wait.
how?
stop.
You want to go.
I will make you stronger.
you can not.
stop.
You can't use it yet.
I will make you stronger.
Your hips are moving.
Put your knees on top.
stop.
Show me your erotic expressions.
You will run away.
You are very angry.
stop.
What expression is that?
Don't stare at me.
What?
You want to go?
how?
If I say so you can go.
I'm going.
What?
I can not hear you.
I want to hear your voice.
I do not want to say.
If you keep putting on that look, you're going to be pissed off.
hurry up.
how?
I wanna go.
You want to go.
You two let her go.
I do not want to go.
You are a pervert.
stop.
Don't accept it.
you are so cute.
I put her on the bed first.
She feels it inside.
You like this bed, don't you?
You are not good at it.
You should attack her from the inside.
You are very good at it.
I'm not.
You put her to bed early.
Are you sleepy?
You do not want?
do you want to stay here
You should get her wet.
good girl.
you are cute.
You are soaked.
You still do it.
You should put her to bed.
You should get her wet.
You are still wet.
more.
you are so cute.
You should get her wet.
you are cute.
You are dirty.
You are soaked.
what do you want to do?
Do you want to be attacked?
you can sleep.
You want to be attacked.
you are so cute.
You are under attack.
stop.
look at her.
Don't put her in bed.
you are so cute.
You can't touch her.
You are so wet.
you are beautiful.
you are so cute.
You like to be attacked.
stop.
You are so wet.
No.
stop.
You can't touch her.
I don't want to cry.
No.
That's pretty amazing.
I will do it.
I'm not in a good mood.
What's this?
What's this? tell me.
what does it feel like
I have never experienced this.
What's this?
stop.
tell me.
I feel something.
This is...
More violent.
I'm not in a good mood.
stop.
That's pretty amazing.
I will do it.
I am in a good mood.
stop.
Which one is bigger?
You said you wouldn't let me go.
help me.
i will cry.
No.
You like to live forever, don't you?
Do not say!
don't you hurt?
Hey let me read your face.
Do not move.
Admin, put this in.
Let me read your face.
Do you think this will work?
Maybe a little too much.
Because you didn't react well.
That is not true.
I can only say no.
Then, put this in.
what should I do?
Might be great if you drink from here.
sorry.
here we go.
one two.
OMG!
It smells so good!
Manager, that's not enough!
more!
For our friendship!
cheers!
No!
Shake it!
OMG!
do you want to see me
No!
get ready?
If you drink that much, you will get sick.
You want to drink, don't you?
I want to drink.
I can drink.
drink.
It's delicious.
Is this your first experience?
Yes.
Stop talking, stop talking.
do you understand?
look at this mouth.
look at this.
What is in front of you?
Are you not drinking enough?
I want to drink.
You want to drink, don't you?
i want to touch you.
Do not touch me.
Are you not drinking enough?
If you don't do well, I will do it again.
You should drink it right.
Is it tasty?
look at the camera.
I am sick.
I do not know what you're talking about.
Don't do that.
I want to drink.
I am sick.
You didn't say you wanted to drink.
I said.
You should lick it properly.
this is the best.
You are getting bigger and bigger.
You are very good at licking.
You are a soap woman.
You should lick us.
I'm going to sleep.
I am sick.
You should do it correctly.
You know what's in the video, don't you?
I believe everyone wants to see it.
You are a soap woman.
You are a good girl.
Did you spit it out?
You are eating with Manco.
Love Card's Manco.
I will do it now.
go.
You are a good girl.
don't let me go.
Put it a little deeper.
You are eating with Manco.
You are a pervert.
You can give it back to me.
why are you trying to escape
I do not know what you're talking about.
Who said you could let me go?
I will do it.
sorry.
How are you?
You look very comfortable.
Thanks.
You make me feel good.
No.
I can't drink it.
Did you smell it?
The smell in the room was nice.
I'm tired.
I am also very comfortable.
did you like it?
What's your job?
I can't take it anymore.
you want it, don't you?
It's very long.
You put it too much.
No.
open mouth.
It smells good.
Don't take it out.
I can't drink it.
What’s wrong with you?
I told you to drink it.
Why?
too disgusting.
You don't want this anymore, do you?
You want the real thing, don't you?
Come on, get up.
You want the real thing now, don't you?
no I do not.
You see, you haven't done this before.
move.
What?
no i'm fine.
You can't do that.
You almost moved when I put you on the bed.
No, I don't want to.
hurry up.
move.
What?
If you don't move, the manager will get angry.
I can't move.
Why?
did you get out of bed
Yes.
because you feel good
No.
stop.
I will watch you.
You have a mark.
look at me.
You look like a flying squirrel.
Come on, turn your face towards me.
yeah.
This is Aixiang's friend.
Say "eggplant.
hurry up.
yeah.
Aika chased me with her tail.
You are the best.
No no no.
you did it!
May I have your name?
Kota
You lost to Kota?
May I?
i hope you get a lot
What are you doing?
I will do it.
You should go there and do it.
stop.
it's here.
I will do it.
No!
No...
Oh no...
try it.
look at your face.
You look like a cat.
You look like a big cat.
No!
look at me.
You look like a cat.
Oh no!
Don't stop it.
You look like a big cat.
I am excited.
No!
How do you feel now?
Oh no!
I'm glad you're happy.
You look like a big cat.
Oh no!
open your eyes.
You can see it, right?
Oh no!
who is crying
how are you feeling
You should admit it.
Then, everyone does their best.
look!
You must feel good.
Hey!
Don't pretend to be innocent.
You are a bitch.
Oh no!
I can't do this anymore.
Too tight.
I'm boring.
I can not do it.
do it yourself.
This is a headache.
You can do it.
I can not do it.
too painful.
it's in my mouth.
look at me.
I am alone.
which one do you like more?
which one?
I have to call a doctor to do this.
too difficult.
It's so easy.
You start breathing heavily again.
which one do you like more?
you don't like it
Why?
you said.
Let's ask him again.
which one do you like more?
Is your boyfriend still ten sauce?
Ten sauces.
I did it!
how do you feel?
Very good!
I feel great!
I can not hear you.
I am very happy.
I feel great!
no no no!
it's coming!
I'll put this in as well.
Really?
I got it.
no no no!
it's coming!
Oh no!
no no no!
It is heavy.
it hurts.
It stinks!
What a waste!
it's all over.
It's too wasteful, so put it in.
It's a waste.
I do not want.
I'll put it all in.
It's a mess.
You are a bitch.
I will put it in.
You can put it in.
No!
I will put it in.
have a look.
All white.
All wrinkled because of the manager.
are you happy?
look at this.
It's all crumpled, isn't it?
Yes.
God.
There are so many spiders.
so cool.
All white.
This is a photo of a guy having sex with a sexy girl.
Take a good photo of it.
All crumpled.
All white.
I can't do this anymore.
what are you saying?
what happens?
I want to take a look.
What will happen if I do more?
what happens?
I want to take a look.
I can not do it.
I'm so happy.
Do you get weird?
Move yourself.
You can move, right?
I'm so happy.
I heard that Aiko's drawings are very good.
I want to take a look.
is that so?
Show me more.
I'm so happy.
how are you feeling
You can move more.
No no no.
You're going to be weird.
I can't take it anymore.
where do you want to go
tell me.
Tell me where you want it.
where do you want to go
Come on and tell me.
I can't take it anymore.
I'm so glad you gave me so much.
I'm so glad you're back at the beach.
Can you give me this much?
I'm so full
Oh no. You have given her so much.
You are so excited.
I'm going to pay for it.
marvelous.
That's fine.
Hey, the store is closed today.
let's go.
Really?
Isn't it bad?
Yes.
OK
I will do my best.
goodbye.
She is the best host.
I don't think I can do this.
I do not think so.
You are very excited.
I can not.
I'm surprised you didn't make too much noise.
You can hear it.
you are a baby.
you are late! I'm finally here!
sorry!
What are you doing
I'm just going to pick up girls.
You are the worst!
My friend is here!
After the manager leaves, you feel alone.
it is true!
Super famous Internet celebrity!
Did you notice?
I did it.
you are too fat!
Did you notice?
What's with that dress?
Let's get a little closer.
Let's toast!
take it.
For our wonderful gathering today!
Really?
Nice to meet you!
For our wonderful gathering today!
cheers!
It's amazing!
Look at my Aika!
What?
You are not very friendly.
I will get more love from you.
so you should be nice to yourself
You can't say hello to me.
hair.
Do you want to see me perverted?
You want to see me, don't you?
I do!
Why are you showing me?
You are just jealous of me.
What?
I'm a successful soap opera actor.
You're still a soap opera actor.
what are you saying?
You are crazy.
You are jealous of me.
You are crazy!
Is that all you want to say?
I'll show you my perverted side.
You're fine with that, right?
You are so driven.
What?
Hey!
You are too aggressive.
do you want to see this
can you do it?
You are too aggressive.
My arm hurts.
do you want to see this
feels good.
It's hot.
You are so erotic.
more.
I want to see your perverted side.
Really?
You are so erotic.
You are very different from before.
you are so nice.
Do you like erotic people?
I like them.
you are so nice.
do you like that
I love you.
you are so nice.
I hope you do more.
I love you.
you are so nice.
do you want me to do this
I want to do this.
can i do this
I will do it slowly.
Does it hurt?
the weather is too hot.
You want to see my perverted side, don't you?
This is good.
the weather is too hot.
That's great, right?
I can do it.
you are so nice.
do you want me to do this
you can not.
You want me to do this, right?
you are so nice.
I love the way you look when you're angry.
It's not there.
You can't do that yet.
You can do this.
You are the best, right?
You hit me.
you are so nice.
A lot of fun.
I'm starting to get scared.
I want more.
you want more
you are so nice.
can i touch you
more.
more?
It's amazing.
you can not.
come over.
your face.
you are so nice.
I will show you how sexy I am.
You will like me even more.
You're going to show me how sexy you are, right?
show me.
you can not.
look.
You are already in my face.
I feel relieved.
My 130,000 followers.
She is crazy.
Good evening.
Watch me get sexy.
What's wrong?
How are you?
I have to show you more.
I can't see you.
can't you see me
in?
You have a lot of acne.
How are you?
I can see you.
You are crazy.
more.
I will do it.
I feel good!
I gotta go.
Babu, she has 130,000 years to live.
This guy.
I'm so happy.
It drives me crazy.
I want a child.
are you sure?
I believe.
I have a child.
I'm so happy.
I want to do more live streaming.
I gotta go.
It's so sour.
I want to drink this water.
marvelous.
It's hitting me in the throat.
Do you do it yourself?
feels good.
I'm so happy.
I can't live stream.
My followers want to see this.
If you want to see it, please tell me what you want to see.
I'm so happy.
Which one do you want to put in?
I have no idea.
I'll put it here.
Really?
I want to walk behind you.
I do not want.
I'm going to put it here.
Oh no, oh no, I'm about to cum.
i'm about to cum
It's so narrow.
Mao San, are you jealous of me?
never.
You are crazy.
I've been live streaming for 130,000 years.
Oh no, oh no, I'm about to cum.
Some people are jealous of me because I'm so comfortable.
certainly.
more?
more.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
i'm about to cum
Oh no, oh no, oh no.
feels good.
i'm about to cum
Don't orgasm.
You are live.
You are so jealous.
i'm about to cum
Mom, you can't do this.
I want to go to the bathroom.
sit down.
put it in.
i'm about to cum
too difficult.
feels good.
why are you moving?
certainly.
i'm about to cum
You are crazy.
why did you stop
do not stop.
i'm about to cum
There.
I'm very sorry.
You don't like this, do you?
again.
There are so many people watching us.
They are watching us.
I'm so happy.
Please lick me again.
do you like my ass
this is the best.
I'm so happy.
Please stick out your tongue.
Amazing.
It's amazing.
How are you?
I'm okay.
I'm very sorry.
I wanna go.
My mouth feels weird.
sorry.
I'm scared from here.
OMG.
I told you to be quiet.
I'll put it here.
lick it.
I'm scared.
OMG.
Pussy is soaked.
Is she like this?
She had a great time.
I'm a little annoyed.
It's amazing!
don't stop me!
This is good!
I can't stop!
I'm so happy!
Mao Zedong, how do you feel?
feels good!
It felt good, I felt like I was on the verge of an orgasm.
Mao, did you cum again?
Mao Zedong will not come out.
Do not do!
Too tight!
Feel good!
My leg hurts.
Oh no.
I think it's about time.
What's wrong?
I am very happy.
Wait a moment.
let's go there.
Where are you?
here?
come over.
I'm here.
look at me.
Do you know who I am?
Your girlfriend is actually this bitch.
are you happy?
poor girl.
it hurts.
I feel great now.
You are crazy.
Let's go and play there.
don't stop me.
No.
I am going home.
I'm so happy.
look at me.
This is me.
I feel good.
I'm so happy.
Wow! You are too strong!
Do you have such a hobby?
Are you a pervert?
Are you a perverted couple?
You are getting stronger.
look!
Your boyfriend is a pervert.
He's happy to see his girlfriend filming him.
how are you feeling
what do you mean?
Which do you think is better? Aika or me?
This is Aika's best boyfriend.
You are a bad girl.
Which one do you like?
tell me.
It doesn't matter.
Which one do you like?
tell me.
You are getting stronger.
Aika, look!
She is watching.
look!
look! Eka is under attack.
Her boyfriend is a pervert.
are you serious?
can i touch you
Can I?
God!
I can't see it.
let me see.
Love Jia!
You are getting stronger.
let me see your lips.
feels good.
I have never seen such a beautiful baby.
Aika, take a closer look.
Bring it here.
I can't see it.
Amazing.
I am hungry. do you know?
how do you feel?
Are you depressed?
feels good.
I might go to Ai Xiang's husband's house.
No no no.
feels good.
Amazing.
I'm so happy.
I gotta go.
Amazing.
It's a baby.
how do you feel?
do you feel the same way i do
Amazing.
You really interesting.
My mic feels fine.
I am very happy.
It feels better than a microphone.
My mic feels fine too.
Do not move.
feels good.
No no no.
I'm going.
I can't stop.
look at this.
She is having sex with a man.
She is a psychopath.
I'm so happy.
look at this.
Isn't it incredible?
She was surprised to see me.
I didn't expect this to happen.
That's real.
She is very comfortable.
It's nice of you to see my face.
That's real.
I hate Aika.
I'm very wet.
Are you going to make me wet again?
sorry.
this is the best.
feels good.
I am very annoyed.
It's really annoying.
I can not stand it any more.
sorry.
I will give you a lot.
Give me a lot.
it hurts.
look at this.
That's a lot.
There are many.
I'm so happy.
Did you see that?
Are you waiting for me?
I'm getting whiter
look at this.
feels good.
I didn't know there were so many.
I have no idea.
What are you doing?
this is the best.
I'm so happy.
You like a bitch, don't you?
this is the best.
I'm so happy.
feels good.
I can not stand it any more.
do not wake me up.
You are a pervert.
You lick my buns.
It's easy for you.
I can't be with you.
Which one do you like?
You can't live without me.
Let me taste you.
You are dirty.
I will clean you up.
Why are you so soft?
let me in.
Why don't you let me in?
Do you not like it?
tell me to let you in.
tell me you want me.
Can't you say it?
I want you.
again.
you need me.
do you want me
come over.
feels good.
It feels good to be here.
You are so soft.
I knew it.
Let's take a photo.
feels good.
I'm so good.
It feels good to be here.
what should I do?
okokokok...
OK...
Why am I already rested?
what a waste...
OMG!
It is like a blue sky.
I am so sleepy.
Are you still sleepy?
What's wrong?
I'm going to sleep.
Oh no!
feels good.
I am so sleepy.
I'm glad you can use the phrase you used with Kanae.
Let me go! Let me go!
You have a lot of hair!
I'll give you a squeeze.
But you can't take it off, can you?
I want you to take it off.
please.
please!
OMG!
I will take it off.
please!
I am very happy.
look at this.
You have a lot of hair.
You just took it off.
look at this.
Stinks.
What? Does it stink?
Do not say.
Stinks.
Are you in a bad mood?
I feel good.
You look embarrassed.
Don't you feel embarrassed to be looked at like this?
I am very happy.
I'll take it off too.
I will take it off again.
It is flying.
So funny.
I have hair all over my head.
How many times have you taken it off?
I know.
Why are you still in a bad mood?
You really interesting.
I can't take it off yet.
You're still in a bad mood, aren't you?
I can't take it off.
OMG!
I can't believe I can love you.
I feel good.
I am such a woman.
can you give me this
I can not.
help me.
give it to me.
I will hand it over to you.
I can not.
I feel good.
I am such a woman.
help me.
I can not.
i really want to take it off
You are a pervert.
I can not.
stop.
I can't take it off.
It is bitter.
My boyfriend is a pervert.
I can not.
There are many things about me.
You are such a jerk.
You are a psychopath.
But you are with me.
So, stay tuned for the next one.
What?
I will prepare a lot.
what are you saying?